Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Commodore Club Records, 1990-1995 and undated RL.11011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Commodore Club records
1990-1995 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11011
0.6 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The Commodore Club was a network of honorably retired directors and executives of the agency. The collection spans 1990-1995 and includes reunion planning documents, texts of speeches and presentations, photographs and biographical sketches of retired JWT executives. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Collection Overview
The collection spans 1990-1995 and includes reunion planning documents, texts of speeches and presentations, photographs and biographical sketches of retired JWT executives. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Arrangement
Organized chronologically.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Commodore Club Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1990-1995
Advertising executives; Advertising executives -- United States; Advertising agencies -- Executives; Retiree networks; Retirees; Retired executives; Retired executives -- United States; Reunions -- United States; Retirees -- Social networks; Reunions; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; J. Walter Thompson Company -- Management; J. Walter Thompson Company -- Employees; J. Walter Thompson Company
- JWT at Duke, Retired Directors' Meeting, 1990; 3 folders (Box 1)
- Photographs, 1993 and undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
- Remarks by Ellen Gartrell, JWT Board Meeting, Duke University, 1992 (Box 1)
- Reunion at Duke, 1990 (Box 1)
- Reunion, Duke University (second annual), 1991 (Box 1)
- Reunion, Stratford, England, 1992 (Box 1)
- Reunion, Stratford, England, 1992 (Box 2)
- Reunion, Troutbeck N.Y., 1993 (Box 2)
- Reunion, Mas de Torrent, Spain, 1994 (Box 2)
- Reunions, 1994-1995 (Box 2)
- Reunion, 1995 (Box 2)